[
    {
        "question": "ويليام",
        "response": "و ي ل ي ا م"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "ن ا م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "response": "ل و ف ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايرين",
        "response": "ا ي ر ي ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "ا س ت ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "همتارو",
        "response": "ه م ت ا ر و"
    },
    {
        "question": "الويفيا",
        "response": "ا ل و ي ف ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "ن و ي ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "رايلي",
        "response": "ر ا ي ل ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ال",
        "response": "ا ل"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاو",
        "response": "ل ا و"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "response": "م ا د ا ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوريتشي",
        "response": "ي و ر ي ت ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتاتشي",
        "response": "ا ي ت ا ت ش ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "توبي",
        "response": "ت و ب ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نوبارا",
        "response": "ن و ب ا ر ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "ل ي ف ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاشيراما",
        "response": "ه ا ش ي ر ا م ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "بوروتو",
        "response": "ب و ر و ت و"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوسوب",
        "response": "ي و س و ب"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريم",
        "response": "ر ي م"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوتشيها شيسوي",
        "response": "ا و ت ش ي ه ا ش ي س و ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيد",
        "response": "ك ي د"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكاسا",
        "response": "م ي ك ا س ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "دانزو",
        "response": "د ا ن ز و"
    },
    {
        "question": "وينغ",
        "response": "و ي ن غ"
    },
    {
        "question": "تينشيهان",
        "response": "ت ي ن ش ي ه ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "بيكوهان",
        "response": "ب ي ك و ه ا ن"
    },
    {
        "question": "كازيكاجي",
        "response": "ك ا ز ي ك ا ج ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيرايا",
        "response": "ج ي ر ا ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كازيكاجي",
        "response": "ك ا ز ي ك ا ج ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوكومي",
        "response": "ك و ك و م ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غيو",
        "response": "غ ي و"
    },
    {
        "question": "تشيو",
        "response": "ت ش ي و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساسوري",
        "response": "س ا س و ر ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيزوكو",
        "response": "ن ي ز و ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميدوريا",
        "response": "م ي د و ر ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيجي",
        "response": "ن ي ج ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "ا س ت ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليزا",
        "response": "ل ي ز ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاغويا",
        "response": "ك ا غ و ي ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هينا",
        "response": "ه ي ن ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "الوكا",
        "response": "ا ل و ك ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيناتا",
        "response": "ه ي ن ا ت ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "زينتسو",
        "response": "ز ي ن ت س و"
    },
    {
        "question": "رينغوكو",
        "response": "ر ي ن غ و ك و"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "ل ي ف ا ي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كورتا",
        "response": "ك و ر ت ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيسوكا",
        "response": "ه ي س و ك ا"
    },
    {
       "question": "انوس",
        "response": "ا ن و س"
    },
    {
       "question": "بياكوغان",
        "response": "ب ي ا ك و غ ا ن"
    },
    {
       "question": "شوكو",
        "response": "ش و ك و"
    },
    {
       "question": "ديكو",
        "response": "د ي ك و"
    },
    {
       "question": "يامي",
        "response": "ي ا م ي"
    },
    {
       "question": "فانجانس",
        "response": "ف ا ن ج ا ن س"
    },
    {
       "question": "يوليوس",
        "response": "ي و ل ي و س"
    },
    {
       "question": "تسوموغو",
        "response": "ت س و م و غ و"
    },
    {
       "question": "نانامي",
        "response": "ن ا ن ا م ي"
    },
    {
       "question": "ايزن",
        "response": "ا ي ز ن"
    },
    {
       "question": "زاراكي",
        "response": "ز ا ر ا ك ي"
    },
    {
       "question": "اوراهارا",
        "response": "ا و ر ا ه ا ر ا"
    },
    {
       "question": "اينوي",
        "response": "ا ي ن و ي"
    },
    {
       "question": "غوهان",
        "response": "غ و ه ا ن"
    },
    {
       "question": "كيريلين",
        "response": "ك ي ر ي ل ي ن"
    },
    {
       "question": "هيناتسورو",
        "response": "ه ي ن ا ت س و ر و"
    },
    {
       "question": "ر ي ت ش ي ل",
       "response": "ر ي ت ش ي ل"
}
]